National American Woman Suffrage Association Records
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- General Correspondence, 1839-1961 (Box 1-36, Reel 1-24)
  - May, Samuel J.
  - May, Sarah R.
  - Mead, Edwin D.
  - Mead, Elizabeth S.
  - Mead, Kate Campbell-Hurd
  - Mead, Lucia Ames
  - Melik, Zaven
  - Meredith, Ellis
  - Merriam, Lovina
  - Merrick, Jennie S.
  - Michigan suffrage associations
  - Miles, Gertrude E.
  - Miller, Anne F.
  - Miller, Elizabeth S.
  - Miller, Leo
  - Mills, Harriet M.
  - Minnesota suffrage associations
  - Mississippi suffrage associations
  - Missouri suffrage associations
  - Mitchell, Agnes
  - Mitchell, Charles A.
  - Mitchell, Evelyn
  - Mitchell, Maria
  - Mitford, Eveline
  - Moffat, Adeline
  - Molineux, Maria A.
  - Montana suffrage associations
  - Moore, A. T. (Box 21, Reel 13)
  - Moore, Henrietta G.
  - Moore, Laura
  - Moore, Mary E.
  - Moore, Mary T.
  - Moors, Ethel P.
  - Moors, John F.
  - Moors, Virginia F.
  - Morgan, Ann
  - Morgan Memorial, Inc.
  - Morrisson, Mary Foulke
  - Mosher, Alfrieda M.
  - Mosher, Eliza M.
  - Mott, Lucretia (Box 21, Reel 14)
  - Münter, Johanne
  - Murdoch, Marion
  - Murphy, Pat
  - Murray, Helen G.
  - Mussey, Ellen S.
  - Mussey, Henry R.
  - Mussey, June B.
  - Mussey, Mabel H. B.
  - Nathan, Maud
  - National League of Women Voters
  - Nebraska suffrage associations
  - Nelson, Julia B.
  - Nevada suffrage associations
  - Newcomb, James P.
  - Newhall, Emma
  - New Hampshire suffrage associations
  - New Jersey suffrage associations
  - New York State suffrage associations
    - 1 of 4
    - 2 of 4
    - 3 of 4
    - 4 of 4
  - New York State Women's Relief Corps Home (Box 22, Reel 14)
  - Nicolay, Helen
  - Noble, Edmund
  - Noble, Lydia
  - Norris, George W.
  - North Dakota suffrage associations
  - Norton, Elizabeth
  - Nowell, Allen M.
  - Nowell, Annie C.
  - Obenchain, Lida C.
  - Oberlin College
  - O'Connor, Jessie Lloyd
  - O'Connor, Lillian
  - Officers, Board of, NAWSA
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - O'Hare, Frank P.
  - O'Hare, Kate Richards
  - Ohio suffrage associations
  - Oklahoma suffrage associations
    - 1 of 3
    - 2 of 3
    - 3 of 3
  - Olmstead, Margaret T.
  - Oregon suffrage associations
  - Osborne, Cyrus A.
  - O'Shee, Mary F.
  - O'Sullivan, Mary K.
  - Owen, Narcissa
  - Pabst, Bertha (Box 23, Reel 15)
  - Paeff, Bashka
  - Page, Anne L.
  - Page, Charles E.
  - Page, Edna R.
  - Page, Mary Hutcheson
  - Paige, Mabeth H.
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - Palacios, Juana
  - Pankhurst, E. Sylvia
  - Papazian, Bertha S.
    - 1 of 9
    - 2 of 9
    - 3 of 9
    - 4 of 9
    - 5 of 9
    - 6 of 9
    - 7 of 9
    - 8 of 9
    - 9 of 9
  - Papazian, Garabed H.
  - Park, Alice
  - Park, Maud Wood
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - Parker, Louise M. (Box 24, Reel 15)
  - Parsons, Abby
  - Parsons, Anna
  - Patchin, Hannah T.
  - Patridge, Lelia E.
  - Patten, Georgie T.
  - Paul, Alice
  - Peabody, Elisabeth
  - Pearry, Edward
  - Pease, F. W.
  - Peck, Mary Gray
    - Various correspondents
      - 1 of 6
      - 2 of 6 (Box 24, Reel 16)
      - 3 of 6
      - 4 of 6
      - 5 of 6
      - 6 of 6
    - Catt, Carrie Chapman
    - Hay, Mary Garrett
    - Hyde, Clara
      - 1 of 6
      - 2 of 6
      - 3 of 6
      - 4 of 6
      - 5 of 6
      - 6 of 6
    - Park, Maud Wood
    - Slade, Caroline
    - Wilson, Justina
  - Peffer, William A. (Box 25, Reel 16)
  - Pellet, Sarah
  - Penfield, S. Adella
  - Pennsylvania suffrage associations
  - Perkins, Frances
  - Perry, Annie F.
  - Phelps, Elizabeth S.
  - Philbrick, Inez C.
  - Phillips, Lena M.
  - Pierce, Philander
  - Piersol, Florence L.
  - Pinckard, Mrs. James S.
  - Pinkham, Henry W.
  - Pinkham, Louisa
  - Pinkham, Wenona O.
  - Pitman, Mira H.
  - Platt, William
  - Pollock, R. M.
  - Porritt, Annie G. (Box 25, Reel 17)
  - Porter, C. V.
  - Post, Alice T.
  - Powell, Anna R.
  - Powell, Mary L.
  - Powell, Rose A.
  - Powers, Madeleine D.
  - Prenn, Joseph
  - Presidents of state suffrage organizations
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - Priest, Alice L.
  - The Public
  - Purington, L. C.
  - Putnam, A. P.
  - Putnam, Eliza O.
  - Putnam, Helen C.
  - Queen, Julia
  - Quimby, Etta
  - Quirk, Hilda H.
  - Rankin, Jeannette
  - Ransom, E. B.
  - Ransom, Eliza T.
  - Ray, Josephine H.
  - Raymore, Charles F.
  - Reid, Ada Chree
  - Reilly, Caroline I.
  - Reines, Bernard
  - Reynolds, Minnie J. (Box 26, Reel 17)
  - Rhode Island suffrage associations
  - Rich, Mary P.
  - Richards, Laura E.
  - Richards, Lysander S.
  - Richardson, Dorothea
  - Richardson, Helen L.
  - Richardson, Margaret F.
  - Richardson, William H., Jr.
  - Rine, Victor
  - Ripley, Ida S.
  - Roback, A. A.
  - Robbins, Charlotte M.
  - Robertson, John Affleck
  - Robins, Elizabeth
  - Robins, Margaret D.
  - Robinson, Harriet H.
  - Robinson, Helen R.
  - Robinson, J. A. M.
  - Robinson, May
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - Robinson, Donald M.
  - Robson, Mrs. George A.
  - Rock, Jo
  - Roderick, Virginia
  - Roewer, George E.
  - Roewer, Rosa H.
  - Rogers, Anne K.
  - Rogers, Edith E.
  - Rogers, Elizabeth
  - Rogers, Emma W.
  - Rogers, Fanny
  - Rogers, Lily
    - 1 of 3
    - 2 of 3
    - 3 of 3
  - Rogers, Meyric R.
  - Rogers, Reynold
  - Rollins, Joseph
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor
  - Ross, Ishbel (Box 26, Reel 18)
  - Rowe, L. S.
  - Roworth, Harriet J. (Box 27, Reel 18)
  - Rubin, Joseph
  - Russell, Frances
  - Russell, Mrs. Henry H.
  - Russian. H. E.
  - Ryan, Agnes E.
  - Sabin, Florence R.
  - St. Louis Star
  - Salvemini, Gaetano
  - Sanders, Elaine G.
  - Santesson, Hans S.
  - Sargent, Amy
  - Sargent, John T.
  - Sarkissian, Garabed
  - Sarkissian, Koharig
  - Sarkissian, Mihran
  - Sarkissian, Rachel
  - Schofield, Emma F.
  - Scholtz, Luisa J. de
  - Schurz, Carl
  - Schwimmer, Franciska
  - Schwimmer, Rosika
    - 1 of 3
    - 2 of 3
    - 3 of 3
  - Scott, John
  - Scudder, Vida D.
  - Searchlight Publishing Co.
  - Sears, Eloise A.
  - Sears, Ruth W.
  - Sender, Tony
  - Severance, Caroline M.
  - Sewall, Harriet W.
  - Sewall, May Wright
  - Sewall, Samuel E.
  - Shafter, Bertha
  - Shattuck, Harriette R.
  - Shaw (Anna Howard) annuity fund
  - Shaw, Anna Howard
    - 1887
    - 1888-1914
    - 1915
    - 1916, Feb.-June
    - 1916, July-1917, undated
  - Shaw, Helen A. (Box 28, Reel 18)
  - Shaw, Pauline Agassiz
  - Shaw, Mrs. Robert G.
  - Sheldon, Elizabeth
  - Shelley, Rebecca
  - Sherman, William
  - Sherwin, Belle
  - Sherwood, Carrie S.
  - Shirley, Hildegarde
  - Sholes, C. Latham
  - Shouse, Jouett
  - Shuler, Nettie R.
  - Siebker, Sophie A.
  - Simmons, Ethel
  - Simmons, Laura
  - Simmons, Noah
  - Simms, L. O.
  - Simpson, M.
  - Sinclair, Mary C.
  - Sinclair, Upton
  - Sisson, Daisy C.
  - Skinner, C. R.
  - Slack, Charles W.
  - Slade, Caroline
  - Slatterly, H. M. (Box 28, Reel 19)
  - Sleeper, Mary P.
  - Small, Sabina
  - Smith, Abby H.
  - Smith, Eliza Kennedy
  - Smith, Ethel M.
  - Smith, Jane E. W.
  - Smith, Judith W.
  - Smith, Julia E.
  - Smith, Zilpha D.
  - Smithsonian Institution
  - Snow, Agnes K.
  - Snow, D. B.
  - Snow, Jane C.
  - Snyder, Lucy A.
  - Society of the Descendants of Early New England Negroes
  - Solano, Marie A.
  - Soule, N. E.
  - South Dakota suffrage associations
  - Southwell, May Knight
  - Spalding, Eliza
  - Spencer, Anna G.
  - Spinner, Francis Elias
  - Spofford, Ainsworth Rand
  - Spofford, Florence P.
  - Spofford, Sarah P.
  - Spooner, Thomas
  - Spooner, W. R.
  - Sprague, Julia A.
  - Stantial, Edna Lamprey
  - Stanton, Byron
  - Stanton, Elizabeth Cady (Box 29, Reel 19)
  - State congressional chairmen, NAWSA
  - Stearns, Ellen Abbott
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - Stearns, Sarah B.
  - Stearns, William O.
  - Stebbins, G. B.
  - Stevens, Henry B.
  - Stevens, Mrs. L. M. N.
  - Stewart, Cora Wilson
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - Stewart, Ella S.
  - Stewart, John W.
  - Stickney, George
  - Stilson, S. L.
  - Stoddard, William Leavitt
  - Straus, Dorothy
  - Strauss, Anna L.
  - Strong, Anna Louise
  - Strong, Sydney
  - Sturge, Adolphus
  - Sunderland, Jabez T.
  - Sutherland, Grovenia
  - Svèhla, Edith W.
  - Talbot, Marion
  - Talbot, Thomas
  - Tallant, Alice W.
  - Tapley, Alice P.
  - Taylor, Violet F.
  - Tchaykovsky, N. W.
  - Tchobanian, A.
  - Teasel, Maria H.
  - Tennessee suffrage associations
  - Texas suffrage associations
  - Thayer, Mrs. B. S.
  - Thomas, M. Carey
  - Thomas, Margaret H.
  - Thomas, Marguerite L.
  - Thomas, Mary B. (Box 29, Reel 20)
  - Thompson, A. Beatrice
  - Thompson, Francis N.
  - Thompson, George
  - Thompson, Gertrude D. S.
  - Thompson, Rose E.
  - Tillinghast, Anna C. M.
  - Tilton, Elizabeth (Box 30, Reel 20)
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - Tilton, Theodore
  - Tilton, William
  - Titterton, Frances
    - 1924-1928
    - 1929-1940
  - Topoozian, Marina
  - Torossian, Alice S.
  - Torossian, Aram
  - Torossian, Hera D.
  - Torricelli, J. B.
  - Townsend, Jessie E.
  - Troy, William H.
  - Tumulty, Joseph P.
  - Turner, Hattie
  - Tyack, Ada M.
  - Union Française Pour le Suffrage des Femmes
  - Universal Franchise Association
  - Upton, Charles H.
  - Upton, Harriet Taylor
  - Van Noorden, Sarah
  - Vermont suffrage associations
  - Villard, Fanny G.
  - Villard, Oswald Garrison
  - Virginia suffrage associations
  - Vivisection Investigation League
  - Voris, A. C.
  - Vrooman, W. A.
  - Wadsworth, James Wolcott (1872-1952)
  - Wald, Lillian D.
  - Walker, Amasa
  - Walker, Joseph
  - Walker, Lola
  - Wallcut, Robert F.
  - Walsh, David I.
  - Ware, Charlotte B.
  - Ware, Robert A.
  - Warren, L. D.
  - Washington suffrage associations
  - Wattles, John D.
  - Waxman, Samuel M.
  - Webb, Richard D.
  - Weber, A. H.
  - Webster, Mary P.
  - Weeks, George F. (Box 31, Reel 20)
  - Weld, Theodore Dwight
  - Welker, Mary P.
  - Weller, Charles F.
  - Weller, Eugenia
  - Weller, Katherine
  - Wellman, C. P.
  - Wells, Kate G.
  - Wells, Marguerite M.
  - West, Charles W.
  - West Virginia suffrage associations (Box 31, Reel 21)
  - Wheelock, Lucy
  - Whipple, Charles K.
  - Whitaker, Robert
  - Whitcomb, Camilla G.
  - White, Armenia S.
  - White, Martha E. D.
  - Whitehead, Celia B.
  - Whiting, Lilian
  - Whitney, Anne
  - Whittier, Florence E.
  - Wilbour, Charlotte B.
  - Wilcox, Hamilton
  - Wilde, C.
  - Wildman, J. K.
  - Willard, Frances E.
  - Willard, Mabel C.
  - Williams, Abram
  - Williams, Annie Laurie
  - Williams, Charl O.
  - Wilson, Alda H.
  - Wilson, Butler R.
  - Wilson, Halsey W. (Box 32, Reel 21)
  - Wilson, Henry
  - Wilson, Justina
  - Wilson, Woodrow
  - Winslow, Gertrude L.
  - Winsor, Mary
  - Winston, Edward M.
  - Wisconsin suffrage associations
  - Wise, Louise Waterman
  - Wise, Stephen S.
  - Wolcott, Roger
  - Woman Citizen Corp.
  - Woman's Christian Temperance Union
  - Woman's Column
    - Alabama-Illinois
    - Indiana-Maryland (Box 32, Reel 22)
    - Massachusetts (Box 33, Reel 22)
    - Michigan-New York
    - Ohio
    - Oregon-Utah
    - Vermont-Wyoming
    - Foreign countries
  - Woman's Journal (Box 34, Reel 22)
    - 1862-1893
    - 1902-1907
    - 1910
    - 1911
    - 1912
    - 1913, 1 of 7
    - 1913, 2 of 7
    - 1913, 3 of 7
    - 1913, 4 of 7 (Box 34, Reel 23)
    - 1913, 5 of 7
    - 1913, 6 of 7
    - 1913, 7 of 7
    - 1913, 1 of 4 (Box 35, Reel 23)
    - 1913, 2 of 4
    - 1913, 3 of 4
    - 1913, 4 of 4
    - 1914
    - 1915
    - 1913 (Box 35, Reel 24)
    - 1917
    - 1916
    - 1926-1960
    - Undated
  - Woman's National Committee for Law Enforcement (Box 36, Reel 24)
  - Woman's rights conventions
  - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom
  - Women's Trade Union League of America
  - Wood, Mary
  - Wood, Samuel N.
  - Woodbury, Benjamin C.
  - Woods, Amy
  - Woods, Kate T.
  - Woodward, Helen L.
  - Woodward, Margaret
  - Woodward, Marion L.
  - Woodward, Samuel B.
  - Woolley, John
  - Woolley, Mary E.
  - World Association of Mothers for Peace
  - World's Columbian Exposition (1893), Chicago, Ill.
  - World's Woman's Christian Temperance Union
  - Wright, D. Thew
  - Wright, Elizur
  - Wright, Henry C.
  - Wright, Martha C.
  - Wright, W. W.
  - Wright, William B.
  - Wyman, Lillie C.
  - Wynner, Edith
  - Wyoming suffrage associations
  - Yaktann, Rose
  - Yates, Elizabeth Upham
    - 1 of 4
    - 2 of 4
    - 3 of 4
    - 4 of 4
  - Yeaton, Alice L.
  - Young, Louise M.
  - Young, Rose
  - Younger, Maud
  - Zakian, A. S.
  - Zakrzewska, Marie
  - Zottoli, Frank M.
  - Unidentified
- Subject File, 1851-1953 (Box 37-80, OV 1, Reel 24-58)
  Minutes, press releases, resolutions, correspondence, subscription lists, telegrams, printed matter, newsletters, notes, telegrams, and scrapbook pages relating mainly to state and local suffrage organizations and leaders in the movement. Includes a large number of published writings and photographs.
  - Abbott, Grace (Box 37, Reel 24)
  - Adams, Abigail
  - Addams, Jane
    - 1 of 5
    - 2 of 5
    - 3 of 5 (Box 37, Reel 25)
    - 4 of 5
    - 5 of 5
  - Alcott, Louisa May
  - Algeo, Sara M.
    - 1 of 9
    - 2 of 9
    - 3 of 9
    - 4 of 9
    - 5 of 9
    - 6 of 9
    - 7 of 9
    - 8 of 9 (Box 38, Reel 25)
    - 9 of 9
  - Alger, Horatio
  - Allen, Florence E.
  - American Anti-Slavery Society (Box 38, Reel 26)
  - American Equal Rights Association
  - American Purity Alliance
  - American Woman Suffrage Association
    - 1 of 3
    - 2 of 3
    - 3 of 3
  - Ames, Charles G.
  - Anderson, Elizabeth G.
  - Anderson, Mary
  - Andrews, Fannie F.
  - Anthony, Susan B.
    - 1 of 7
    - 2 of 7 (Box 39, Reel 26)
    - 3 of 7
    - 4 of 7
    - 5 of 7
    - 6 of 7
    - 7 of 7
  - Antisuffrage literature
    - 1 of 36
    - 2 of 36 (Box 39, Reel 27)
    - 3 of 36
    - 4 of 36
    - 5 of 36
    - 6 of 36
    - 7 of 36
    - 8 of 36 (Box 40, Reel 27)
    - 9 of 36
    - 10 of 36
    - 11 of 36
    - 12 of 36
    - 13 of 36
    - 14 of 36
    - 15 of 36
    - 16 of 36 (Box 40, Reel 28)
    - 17 of 36
    - 18 of 36
    - 19 of 36 (Box 41, Reel 28)
    - 20 of 36
    - 21 of 36
    - 22 of 36
    - 23 of 36
    - 24 of 36
    - 25 of 36
    - 26 of 36 (Box 42, Reel 28)
    - 27 of 36
    - 28 of 36
    - 29 of 36
    - 30 of 36
    - 31 of 36
    - 32 of 36
    - 33 of 36 (Box 42, Reel 29)
    - 34 of 36
    - 35 of 36
    - 36 of 36
  - Applegarth, Margaret T. (Box 43, Reel 29)
  - Arizona suffrage associations
  - Arkansas suffrage associations
    - 1 of 3
    - 2 of 3
    - 3 of 3
  - Army Nurse Association
  - Association for Moral and Social Hygiene
  - Astor, Nancy Witcher Langhorne Astor, Viscountess
  - Atkinson, Wilmer
  - Babcock, Elnora
  - Baker, Newton D.
  - Barrows, Samuel J.
  - Barton, Clara
  - Bates, Katharine L.
  - Becker, Lydia
  - Beebe, C. William
  - Bequests
    - Avery, Susan H.
    - Ballinger, Rebecca H.
    - Bates, Octavia
    - Bidwell, Annie E. K.
      - 1 of 3
      - 2 of 3
      - 3 of 3
    - Brown, Frances Fort
    - Buckley, Lila S.
    - Coggeshall, Mary J.
    - Dickinson, Melissa
      - 1 of 6
      - 2 of 6
      - 3 of 6 (Box 44, Reel 30)
      - 4 of 6
      - 5 of 6
      - 6 of 6
    - Leslie, Mrs. Frank
    - McCall, Sarah J.
    - MacLochlin, Addie C. H.
    - Palmer, Thomas W.
    - White, Nettie Lovisa
  - Berry, Martha (Box 45, Reel 30)
  - Birdsall, Mrs. W. E.
  - Biscoe, Helen M.
  - Björkman, Frances M.
  - Bloomer, Amelia
  - Boissevain, Inez M.
  - Bonefield, Margaret
  - Bones, Marietta M.
  - Books relating to woman suffrage
    - 1 of 5
    - 2 of 5
    - 3 of 5
    - 4 of 5
    - 5 of 5
  - Borah, William Edgar
  - Bowles, Ada C.
  - Boyer, Ida Porter
    - 1 of 9
    - 2 of 9
    - 3 of 9
    - 4 of 9
    - 5 of 9
    - 6 of 9
    - 7 of 9
    - 8 of 9
    - 9 of 9 (Box 45, Reel 31)
  - Bradford, Mary C. C.
  - Brandeis, Alice
  - Bray, Maria H. (Box 46, Reel 31)
  - Breckinridge, Mrs. Desha
  - Brent, Margaret
  - Bridges, Harry
  - Brooks, Phillips
  - Brown, John
  - Brown, Mrs. Larue
  - Bryant, William Cullen
  - Buck, Pearl S.
  - Bushnell, Katharine C.
  - Buss, Frances M.
  - Butler, Benjamin F.
    - 1 of 3
    - 2 of 3
    - 3 of 3
  - Butler, Josephine E.
    - 1 of 3
    - 2 of 3
    - 3 of 3
  - California Civic League
  - Cambridge (Mass.) League of Women Voters
  - Cambridge Political Equality Association, Cambridge, Mass.
    - 1 of 3
    - 2 of 3
    - 3 of 3
  - Canadian suffrage organizations
  - Calder, Ellen M.
  - Carroll, Anna E.
  - Cather, Willa
  - Catholics and woman suffrage
  - Catlin, Mary L.
  - Chadwick, John W.
  - Chant, Laura O. (Box 47, Reel 32)
  - Chapman, Maria W.
  - Child labor amendment
  - Clapp, Moses E.
  - Coleman, George W.
  - College Equal Suffrage League
    - 1 of 5
    - 2 of 5
    - 3 of 5
    - 4 of 5
    - 5 of 5
  - College women
  - Congressional committees
    - 1 of 13
    - 2 of 13
    - 3 of 13
    - 4 of 13
    - 5 of 13
    - 6 of 13
    - 7 of 13
    - 8 of 13
    - 9 of 13
    - 10 of 13 (Box 48, Reel 32)
    - 11 of 13
    - 12 of 13
    - 13 of 13 (Box 48, Reel 33)
  - Congressional Union
    - Anti-Democratic party policy of Congressional Union
    - Armes, Marie T.
    - Atkinson, Wilmer
    - Bates, Helen N.
    - Beard, Mary R.
    - Belmont, Alva E.
    - Benedict, Crystal Eastman
    - Bly, Mrs. Vincent
    - Booth, Bess
    - Bounfield, Mrs. M. O.
    - Brannan, Eunice Dana
    - Breckinridge, Mrs. Desha
    - Brown, Olympia
    - Burns, Lucy
    - California Woman's State Democratic League
    - Catt, Carrie Chapman
    - Chamberlain, George E.
    - Churchill, Mrs. Winston
    - Clark, Nellie Sawyer
    - Clarke, J. K.
    - Cranston, Martha S.
    - Day, Katharine B.
    - Diggs, Annie L.
    - Dixon, Mary Bartlett
    - Dock, Lavinia L.
    - Duniway, Abigail S.
    - Eichelberger, Bessie R.
    - Equal Franchise Society of Philadelphia, Philadelphia, Pa.
    - Feickert, Mrs. E. E.
    - Fitzgerald, Susan W.
    - Forrest, Marie Moore
    - Frost, Susan P.
    - Funk, Antoinette
    - Gardener, Helen H.
    - Gillett, Emma M.
    - Hallinan, Charles Thomas
    - Hanna, Mrs. M. A.
    - Harris, Mrs. Joel Chandler
    - Hauser, Elizabeth J.
    - Hepburn, Katharine H.
    - Hooker, Edith H.
    - Irwin, Inez H.
    - Jenks, Agnes M.
    - Jones, D. T. H.
    - Kennedy, Mrs. C. R. (Box 49, Reel 33)
    - Kenny, Catherine
    - Kent, Elizabeth T.
    - King, Cora Smith
    - Leonard, Gertrude
    - Lewis, Cora G.
    - Lewis, Dora
    - Lewis, Julia
    - McCormick, Katharine D.
    - McCormick, Ruth Hanna
      - 1 of 2
      - 2 of 2
    - McKee, Sue M.
    - Magown, Jeanne B.
    - Martin, Anne H.
    - Massachusetts Woman Suffrage Association
    - Men's Equal Suffrage League (District of Columbia)
    - Miller, Helen G.
    - Mitchell, Lucretia
    - Mogué, Alice L. H.
    - Morgan, Laura P.
    - Morrisson, Mary Foulke
    - Mott, Isabella
    - NAWSA
      - Policy differences with
      - Separation from
      - Vote on auxiliary membership
    - National Woman's Party
    - O'Neill, Mrs. E. B.
    - Paul, Alice
    - Peabody, Josephine Preston
    - Perky, K. I.
    - Perry, Emily K.
    - Picketing
    - Prendergast, Agnes
    - Publicity
      - 1916
      - 1917
        - 1 of 4
        - 2 of 4
        - 3 of 4 (Box 50, Reel 33)
        - 4 of 4
      - General
        - 1 of 2
        - 2 of 2
    - Rastall, Fanny H.
    - Reavill, Jeanette M.
    - Robinson, Helen R.
    - Rogers, Elizabeth
    - Ruutz-Rees, Caroline
    - Seldomridge, Harry H.
    - Shaw, Anna Howard (Box 50, Reel 34)
    - Smith, Ethel M.
    - Somerville, Nellie N.
    - Stanwood, Louie
    - Stevens, Doris
    - Thomas, Charles
    - Thomas, Charles S.
    - Trout, Grace Wilbur
    - Upton, Harriet Taylor
    - Vittum, Harriet
    - West Virginia Equal Suffrage Association
    - Whitaker, Edith
    - Whitehouse, Mrs. Norman
    - Whitney, Charlotte A.
    - Wiley, Anna Kelton
    - Young, Ella Flagg
    - Young, Rose
    - Miscellany
    - Printed matter
  - Connecticut suffrage associations (Box 51, Reel 34)
    - 1 of 21
    - 2 of 21
    - 3 of 21
    - 4 of 21
    - 5 of 21
    - 6 of 21
    - 7 of 21
    - 8 of 21
    - 9 of 21
    - 10 of 21
    - 11 of 21 (Box 51, Reel 35)
    - 12 of 21 (Box 52, Reel 35)
    - 13 of 21
    - 14 of 21
    - 15 of 21
    - 16 of 21
    - 17 of 21
    - 18 of 21
    - 19 of 21
    - 20 of 21
    - 21 of 21
  - Coolidge, Calvin (Box 53, Reel 36)
  - Cooper, Rose H.
  - Creel, George
  - Crothers, Rachel
  - Czechoslovakia, suffrage in
  - Dargan, Olive Tilford
  - Debs, Eugene V.
  - Democratic Party
  - Douglass, Margaret
  - Druce, Vincent, Jr.
  - Dudley, Mrs. Guilford
  - Dudley, Helena S.
  - Eastman, Max
  - Einstein, Albert
  - Elliott, Maud Howe
  - Emerson, Ralph Waldo
  - English women and the law
  - Equal rights amendment See also Container 76, Woman suffrage amendment
    - 1 of 6
    - 2 of 6
    - 3 of 6
    - 4 of 6
    - 5 of 6
    - 6 of 6
  - Evans, Elizabeth Glendower
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - Fair Tariff League
  - Fiske, Minnie Maddern
  - Florida suffrage associations
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - Forbes, Rose D.
  - Foster, Abby Kelley
  - Fuller, Margaret
  - Gandhi, Mahatma (Box 54, Reel 36)
  - Gardener, Helen H.
    - 1 of 5
    - 2 of 5
    - 3 of 5
    - 4 of 5 (Box 54, Reel 37)
    - 5 of 5
  - Garner, Margaret
  - Garrett, Mary Elizabeth
  - Garrison, William Lloyd
    - 1 of 6
    - 2 of 6
    - 3 of 6
    - 4 of 6
    - 5 of 6
    - 6 of 6
  - Garvin, Lucius F. C.
  - George, Henry
  - Georgia suffrage associations
  - Gillett, Emma M.
  - Gilman, Charlotte P.
    - 1 of 4
    - 2 of 4
    - 3 of 4
    - 4 of 4
  - Gordon, Laura de Force (Box 55, Reel 37)
  - Gougar, Helen M.
  - Graham, Abbie
  - Greeley, Horace
  - Green, Virginia T.
  - Grenfell, Helen L.
  - Grimké, Francis J.
  - Hale, Beatrice Forbes-Robertson (Box 55, Reel 38)
  - Haley, Margaret A.
  - Hall, Florence H.
  - Hamilton, Alice
  - Hammond, Josephine
  - Harbert, Elizabeth B.
  - Harper, Ida Husted
  - Hawaii suffrage associations
  - Hay, Mary Garrett
    - 1 of 3
    - 2 of 3
    - 3 of 3
  - Hayes, Ellen
  - Heaton, Eliza P.
  - Henrotin, Ellen
  - Henshaw, Josiah
  - Higginson, Thomas Wentworth
  - Hoar, George F.
  - Hobhouse, Emily
  - Holley, Sallie
  - Hooper, Lizzie
  - Hovey, Charles F.
  - Howe, Julia Ward
    - 1 of 4
    - 2 of 4
    - 3 of 4
    - 4 of 4
  - Howe, Marie Jenney
  - Hunt, Harriot K.
  - Hutchinson, Anne
  - Illinois suffrage associations
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - Incorporation, certificate of (Box 56, Reel 39)
  - Indiana suffrage associations
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - International Alliance of Women
  - International Alliance of Women for Suffrage and Equal Citizenship
  - International Woman Suffrage Alliance
    - General
      - 1 of 5
      - 2 of 5
      - 3 of 5
      - 4 of 5
      - 5 of 5
    - Printed matter
      - 1 of 9
      - 2 of 9
      - 3 of 9
      - 4 of 9 (Box 56, Reel 40)
      - 5 of 9 (Box 57, Reel 40)
      - 6 of 9
      - 7 of 9
      - 8 of 9
      - 9 of 9
  - Iowa suffrage associations
  - Irwin, Inez H.
  - Jackson, Andrew
  - Jackson, James
  - Jacobs, Pattie Ruffner
  - James, Edward H.
  - Johnson, Ethel M.
  - Johnson, Owen
  - Jones, Harriet B.
  - Kagawa, Toyohiko
  - Kansas suffrage associations
  - Kansas suffrage campaign, 1867
  - Kelley, Florence
  - Kentucky suffrage associations (Box 57, Reel 41)
  - Larcom, Lucy (Box 58, Reel 41)
  - Larimer, William
  - Lenroot, Katharine F.
  - Leslie Woman Suffrage Commission
    - Litigation
      - 1 of 20
      - 2 of 20
      - 3 of 20
      - 4 of 20
      - 5 of 20 (Box 59, Reel 41)
      - 6 of 20
      - 7 of 20
      - 8 of 20
      - 9 of 20 (Box 59, Reel 42)
      - 10 of 20
      - 11 of 20 (Box 60, Reel 42)
      - 12 of 20
      - 13 of 20
      - 14 of 20
      - 15 of 20 (Box 60, Reel 43)
      - 16 of 20 (Box 61, Reel 43)
      - 17 of 20
      - 18 of 20